Snow Revision Star and Call Star and Call
What a nice bridge you make, Jotaro.
Oh, hang on, Jotaro, I
have a very nasty itch.
Scratch it.
Just a little lower.
Even lower.
Yeah, that's it.
But not too hard, mind you.
Mr.
Joestar?
Hey, what's the matter?
It honestly feels like
someone's tickling my back!
I can't concentrate much longer like this!
Calm down!
Just perfect.
We've got quite the captive audience.
Mr.
Joestar, keep your voice down.
People are staring.
Keep this up and they'll
think you've gone nuts.
You think I'm screaming
for the hell of it? No! No!
That poor man.
Why don't we give him some change?
Why are they throwing money?
I pity them.
Old relatives like that can be tough.
That is so true.
Kakyoin, go buy the TV.
Let's get out of this crowd.
Right.
Is this your store?
Yes, it is.
I'd like to buy that TV.
Unbelievable.
Kakyoin's Hierophant and Polnareff's
Chariot Shrunk themselves
to a microscopic level and
infiltrated Joestar's body they
Intend to fight me I can see them
they're traveling through the
bloodstream And heading toward
the brainstem right to my lovers
quickly we don't have long
before the flesh but in mr.
Joestar's brain eats Let's clean through.
Hurry, you two.
Alley-up.
All right.
Do it, Mr. Chostar. Right.
Hermit Purple!
These are...
The Flesh Bud's tentacles. Great.
We finally made it to the brain stem,
but the Flesh Bud's already taken over.
Damn it!
Just look at that fiend.
He's using those weird
claws of his to knead Mr.
Joestar's brain cells into a gooey mash,
and I bet he's going to
feed it to the flesh bud.
We have to destroy him and tear out all
the flesh bud's roots as fast as we can,
or else they'll completely
devour his brain.
D 'accord, I'll Jolyne him to rib it!
You know, on second thought, I think
a finer cut should do the trick.
I'll turn you into a lump of pate!
No, you don't!
Now!
He did it!
No, not quite.
I gotta say, Kakyoin,
that thing's pretty fast.
But luckily for us, I've
already figured him out.
If that's all the little beast
has, then he's no match for...
Polnareff!
Who are you talking to?
What? Huh?
Polnareff, that's not me.
And that wasn't the real stand.
Look, it's melting away.
What the...
I'm the Lovers!
Hold the wreath!
He disguised himself
using the brain cells. Mr.
Joestar's brain cells.
Somehow,
that thing was able to use
the collection of needed
brain cells to disguise
himself as my hierophant green.
And since he can mold his cells at will,
all you destroyed was a decoy
made of those brain cells.
You hit the nail on the head, And
you dummies completely fell for it!
Come on!
Pull your head out of your ass, would ya?
You better shine those
shoes right, Jotaro!
I'm in such a good mood,
I can hardly stand it.
So I'm gonna need you to
keep polishing these shoes
until they're shining as
brightly as I feel right now.
Do you think you can handle
that, my little sycophant?
You can stop polishing
when that magnificent
sun up in the sky makes
these puppies sparkle.
Also, I want you to use
your tongue to shine them.
Hey, you bastard!
What are you writing in there?
You're looking at your tab.
And you're gonna pay in full.
I wrote it down, so I won't forget.
You're a scoundrel, Jotaro.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It'll all be meaningless in the end.
Whoa!
Kakyoin, look!
Check out the decoy's
head that I just opened!
What?
What the hell's going on?
Somehow he's splitting in two.
Listen up.
Here's some advice.
To win in life, one must
thoroughly know oneself.
It's like Aesop's fables when the
unassuming tortoise beats the hare.
The tortoise outruns the
hare because he knows
himself and his abilities
better than anyone else.
Of course, the same applies to me.
I'm no fool.
I know perfectly well I don't
possess the power or speed
necessary to mortally wound
either of you one-on-one.
But remember this!
The spoils belong to those who
admit their own weaknesses!
Emerald Splash!
Did it work?
What?
More decoys are forming
out of the brain cells.
They're multiplying.
But a person can have only one stand,
which means only one of them is real.
That said, where's the real one?
Right here!
Gah!
Emerald splash!
Well, that's not good.
Any closer and I would have been killed.
The more decoys we hit,
the more they multiply.
No! No! It's me! It's me!
It's me! It's me!
It's me!
They're all me!
Can't you tell?
Polnareff, that's enough!
Withdraw your stand now!
I can't just watch you get hurt,
even if you are trying to save me.
No way in hell!
I can't stand the thought of giving
up and watching you die like this!
Are you trying to die?
Withdraw your stand!
Do as I say.
It's over.
You can't quit, Mr.
Chostar.
We'll fight till the end.
Damn.
They all look the same.
Which one is the real one, and
which one of them is the stand?
I can't tell them apart.
The world's biggest stand
is the most
powerful!
Hey, now, take a look at this, Jotaro.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
I would wager an expensive gift like this
would make any girl fall head over heels.
Jotaro, you see that
space there in the glass?
Use your stand to sneak
through and steal the bracelet.
Steal it what don't you understand
moron get a move on if you
know what's good for you i mean i
Don't mind breaking the glass and
taking the bracelet myself then
again if i'm caught i could Be
beaten to a bloody pulp old Joseph
would surely die from the pain
Hurry, would you?
Do it while the salesman's
looking the other way!
Oh, no!
This guy is shoplifting!
Son of a...
Do something.
This guy's shoplifting!
Come on, salesman!
I'll go and get some help!
Please, sir!
Don't let him get away!
Sure thing!
Bastard!
All right, boys!
Where's this thief at?
Who's the culprit?
Is it that guy there? You're?
Talking about that Asian kid.
You know, back where I come from,
when someone steals something,
we chop their fingers off.
Hey, Jotaro, you better not use
your stand against civilians.
PUNKBALL!
Take this!
Despicable!
You dirty thief!
Now you get the hell out of our
country and don't come back!
Good for nothing, asshole!
You do that, we'll allow you to
leave here with your fingers intact!
That was great.
Nicely done, my friend.
Thanks to the commotion you caused,
I was able to get my hands on something
even better than that bracelet.
Huh?
Jojaro!
What the hell are you laughing about?
What's so damn funny?
Huh? Huh?
Nothing.
I'm just a bit excited.
I was laughing because your
punishment has doubled,
and I've been waiting a
while for this moment.
It's just about time for payback, and I
gotta say, it's really got me tingling.
Why, you!
It would seem that we have
something of a misunderstanding.
I'm sorry to say, but your old
man isn't long for this world.
That's the reality you're facing.
How sad.
You don't know us very
well, do you, friend?
And I see you don't know Kakyoin at all.
Come again?
It seems to me you're obsessed
with the notion of knowing oneself.
Yes, that makes sense.
I suppose I'm inclined to agree.
But before you continue pontificating,
think on this for a moment.
There's another adage, know thy
enemy, that's nothing to scoff at.
Can't you see?
My Hierophant has a certain ability.
It has the power to
stretch out its feelers.
And I've been inspecting
every single one of you.
How could I have not noticed
something touching me?
So you're the stand.
Emerald, splash!
Success!
Well, well, what do we have here?
Looks like Kakyoin got
you pretty damn good.
So I'm wondering, will I get
my payback once he's done?
He realized that he's
out of his league and
now he's trying to escape into the artery!
He's trying to escape from Mr.
Joestar's brain! Huh?
Did you say he's leaving? All right!
That's great news, isn't it? Mr.
Joestar, hurry! The Flesh Buds!
Right!
Time for overdrive!
The Flesh Buds vanishing!
Thank God it's gone.
Well, if you ask me,
this whole experience has done a lot
to bring our group closer together.
You're incorrigible, Polnareff.
Hold on a minute!
If that thing's really
trying to leave my brain...
Then wouldn't that imply
that the stand is...
The bastard is returning to its user!
This is bad!
Jotaro has no way of knowing!
What's wrong?
Why are you backing away from me?
Aren't you going to tell me more
about my grandfather's death?
I'd really love to know.
Hey, wait a minute!
What's with the big hurry?
We weren't done talking yet.
No! It couldn't be!
You're not actually trying
to run away, are you?
After all you've done.
Please, Jotaro, sir, forgive me!
I admitted you in.
I'll lie down and lick your boots.
I know I did a bad thing
and I want to change.
You can pummel me as much as
you'd like. Hit me. Kick me.
But please, don't kill me.
I'm begging you to spare my life.
Soon, very soon, the
lovers will return to me.
And this idiot Jotaro
doesn't have a single clue.
Just you wait.
This time it'll enter your brain.
Kakuin can't help you from
hundreds of meters away.
I'll make you suffer pain so horrible
you'll wish you were never born.
It's here!
Now, enter his ear!
I kinda figured you'd go and
try something shitty like this.
Don't you know my Stanstar
Platinum possesses
excellent eyesight and precise reflexes?
You're pathetic.
Didn't you check up on us
at all even a little bit?
No no no no no!
Believe me I wasn't planning anything.
Not against your stance.
Immense power did you just say your stand?
Only your let me explain what
I meant to say is that your
awesome and powerful stand
is far superior to any other.
I knew it didn't stand a
chance so I had it come back.
Just look at what you've done.
You've already She shattered
my arm and leg to pieces.
I can't possibly fight anymore.
I can't even move.
In that case, I guess
I'll take pity on you?
And accept your arm and leg as payment!
for all the low blows
you took out against me.
But only if you swear that you'll never
show your ugly mug in front of us again.
I'll do whatever you say, I promise.
I'll head for some deserted island?
Or I'll go to the ends of the earth!
and never return to bother you.
You'd better not be lying.
The next time I see that face,
it'll get a thousand punches.
I'm not lying!
I would never, ever lie to you!
Get lost.
Let's just hop her over there.
Joe Dario
You're an utter fool!
Just take a look at that girl.
It might interest you
to know that my stand,
the lovers Just went into that girl's ear.
Now he's heading for her brain?
You better not move, Jotaro!
Here's what's about to happen.
I'm gonna stab you in
the back with this knife
and make sure that you're
never able to move again!
Attack me with your star platinum and this
girl's pathetic life
ends right here and now!
But you would never allow such an
innocent child to die, would you?
Oh, good grief.
Go ahead and stab me then. Huh?
Hey, now, did you not hear me?
I just told you not to...
I told you not to move.
What's the matter?
Didn't you say something
about stabbing me?
Like this, right?
My body won't move! Wha... why?
What the...
what is this thing wrapped around me?
I see you didn't notice, as your
stand was trying to make its escape.
Kakyoin tied Hierophant's
tentacle to its leg.
And seeing as those
tentacles stretch all the
way back to your stand
like a string to a kite,
you must have been so self-absorbed
you didn't even notice.
Please, I'm begging you, forgive me!
Ask for forgiveness from
Enyaba, the woman you killed.
But as for me, I never had the
slightest intention of forgiving you.
Dio paid me to cause this madness.
You can have it all.
Good grief.
I know this is blatantly obvious,
but you really are a piece of work.
What you owe me, you can never
even pay back with money!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Your receipt.
You can keep the freakin' change.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They got the money on a bed.
All crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink,
then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings!
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
I just can't shake the feeling
that there's someone out there?
watching us.
Don't you think you might
be worrying a bit too much?
I think he's on to something.
I feel some sort of presence too.
I still haven't been able to shake the
feeling that someone out
there is watching us.
Something's not right, but what is it?